hey guys it's Annie here I'm Fabio and
we're back with another video today's
video we're taking a break from the
singers yeah oh yes let's watch another
eachother decided that's what let's
watch another commercial that many
people have been asking for us to react
to called Manulife Philippines stand up
I think I Manulife you know what man
your life is like an insurance company
oh you think is it I don't know anyway
before we begin we should have liked
this video subscribe to my channel and
survive this channel as well check out
our social media we post a lot of dance
videos our awesome beautiful picture so
conceited
I know okay so here we go they said
there's a major twist for this
commercial I'm not sure if this you just
ruined it for me now I'm gonna be
looking for there's always a twist in
Filipino commercials I know you should
know that already by now dating a
Filipino I have a lot of twists every
day
Oh
[Music]
oh my gosh pony by choice
my process choice is a Senior Seminar
hmm we ah I want to be a stand-up
comedian ha ha they don't have any dad
about they are known to support would
sit down
certainly our contestant Jose so yeah I
am I think I know a McGee committee
auntie absently here yes I know my
family they say wow your family's
complete you have doctors attorneys and
a spanned up comedian so you have a
doctor's appointment and at own
disappointment and disappointment that I
thought I was a joke oh sorry yeah
Nabila so you know nubira know
you know cos I wasn't that good daddy
thanks for everything dad
[Music]
everybody's against put up in ballet go
[Applause]
ours a stands not funny no oh my gosh
that's not funny well I don't know we
were just the ones i assuming it I guess
but I was like this is a drama comedy
now I was ready to cry oh you were
I was because oh my god
anyway so sensitive it was a cute
commercial though it was a good
commercial yeah it was good sorry it's
bothering me you have like one eyelash
that is like pointing down to your
eyeball open where is it now see inside
your eyes it's gonna go through your
veins and go through your heart and it's
gonna stab your heart it's a lot she
could not stop it I don't know what
lashes you have that's what you can
Rochelle is very entertaining that you
guys recommend in the video comment
below again what kind of videos you like
us to react to next sorry we haven't
gone through everything yet but let us
know again next time what kind of video
it's a long list of videos guys a lot
and there's always a lot of new ones we
love it it's just a lot
something like it's here it oh my god
maybe maybe I'm dying to thank you for
watching
oh I will see you next time bye
[Music]